{
  "DeckName": "Katakana Words vol2",
  "LanguageCode": "ja-JP",
  "DeckEnabled": false,
  "Cards": [
    {
      "Question": "ホン",
      "Narration": "hon",
      "Answer": "book"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ジショ",
      "Narration": "jisho",
      "Answer": "dictionary"
    },
    {
      "Question": "テガミ",
      "Narration": "tegami",
      "Answer": "letter"
    },
    {
      "Question": "クルマ",
      "Narration": "kuruma",
      "Answer": "car"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ジテンシャ",
      "Narration": "jitensha",
      "Answer": "bicycle"
    },
    {
      "Question": "デンシャ",
      "Narration": "densha",
      "Answer": "train"
    },
    {
      "Question": "エキ",
      "Narration": "eki",
      "Answer": "station"
    },
    {
      "Question": "マチ",
      "Narration": "machi",
      "Answer": "town"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ヒト",
      "Narration": "hito",
      "Answer": "person"
    },
    {
      "Question": "イヌ",
      "Narration": "inu",
      "Answer": "dog"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ネコ",
      "Narration": "neko",
      "Answer": "cat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "トリ",
      "Narration": "tori",
      "Answer": "bird"
    },
    {
      "Question": "サカナ",
      "Narration": "sakana",
      "Answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "Question": "カイモノ",
      "Narration": "kaimono",
      "Answer": "shopping"
    },
    {
      "Question": "シゴト",
      "Narration": "shigoto",
      "Answer": "work"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ガッコウ",
      "Narration": "gakkou",
      "Answer": "school"
    },
    {
      "Question": "トモダチ",
      "Narration": "tomodachi",
      "Answer": "friend"
    },
    {
      "Question": "カゾク",
      "Narration": "kazoku",
      "Answer": "family"
    },
    {
      "Question": "オンガク",
      "Narration": "ongaku",
      "Answer": "music"
    },
    {
      "Question": "エイガ",
      "Narration": "eiga",
      "Answer": "movie"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ウタ",
      "Narration": "uta",
      "Answer": "song"
    },
    {
      "Question": "オカシ",
      "Narration": "okashi",
      "Answer": "sweets/snacks"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ギュウニュウ",
      "Narration": "gyuunyuu",
      "Answer": "milk"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ミズ",
      "Narration": "mizu",
      "Answer": "water"
    },
    {
      "Question": "アサ",
      "Narration": "asa",
      "Answer": "morning"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ヒル",
      "Narration": "hiru",
      "Answer": "afternoon"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ヨル",
      "Narration": "yoru",
      "Answer": "night"
    },
    {
      "Question": "キョウ",
      "Narration": "kyou",
      "Answer": "today"
    },
    {
      "Question": "アシタ",
      "Narration": "ashita",
      "Answer": "tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "Question": "キノウ",
      "Narration": "kinou",
      "Answer": "yesterday"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ウミ",
      "Narration": "umi",
      "Answer": "sea"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ヤマ",
      "Narration": "yama",
      "Answer": "mountain"
    },
    {
      "Question": "カワ",
      "Narration": "kawa",
      "Answer": "river"
    },
    {
      "Question": "モリ",
      "Narration": "mori",
      "Answer": "forest"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ハナ",
      "Narration": "hana",
      "Answer": "flower"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ハル",
      "Narration": "haru",
      "Answer": "spring"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ナツ",
      "Narration": "natsu",
      "Answer": "summer"
    },
    {
      "Question": "アキ",
      "Narration": "aki",
      "Answer": "autumn"
    },
    {
      "Question": "フユ",
      "Narration": "fuyu",
      "Answer": "winter"
    },
    {
      "Question": "アオ",
      "Narration": "ao",
      "Answer": "blue"
    },
    {
      "Question": "アカ",
      "Narration": "aka",
      "Answer": "red"
    },
    {
      "Question": "シロ",
      "Narration": "shiro",
      "Answer": "white"
    },
    {
      "Question": "クロ",
      "Narration": "kuro",
      "Answer": "black"
    },
    {
      "Question": "キイロ",
      "Narration": "kiiro",
      "Answer": "yellow"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ミドリ",
      "Narration": "midori",
      "Answer": "green"
    },
    {
      "Question": "クツ",
      "Narration": "kutsu",
      "Answer": "shoes"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ボウシ",
      "Narration": "boushi",
      "Answer": "hat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "メガネ",
      "Narration": "megane",
      "Answer": "glasses"
    },
    {
      "Question": "テ",
      "Narration": "te",
      "Answer": "hand"
    },
    {
      "Question": "アシ",
      "Narration": "ashi",
      "Answer": "foot/leg"
    },
    {
      "Question": "メ",
      "Narration": "me",
      "Answer": "eye"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ミミ",
      "Narration": "mimi",
      "Answer": "ear"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ハナ",
      "Narration": "hana",
      "Answer": "nose"
    },
    {
      "Question": "クチ",
      "Narration": "kuchi",
      "Answer": "mouth"
    },
    {
      "Question": "カミ",
      "Narration": "kami",
      "Answer": "hair"
    },
    {
      "Question": "セ",
      "Narration": "se",
      "Answer": "height"
    },
    {
      "Question": "コエ",
      "Narration": "koe",
      "Answer": "voice"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ココロ",
      "Narration": "kokoro",
      "Answer": "heart/mind"
    },
    {
      "Question": "アタマ",
      "Narration": "atama",
      "Answer": "head"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ドウブツ",
      "Narration": "doubutsu",
      "Answer": "animal"
    },
    {
      "Question": "コウエン",
      "Narration": "kouen",
      "Answer": "park"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ウチ",
      "Narration": "uchi",
      "Answer": "home/house"
    },
    {
      "Question": "イエ",
      "Narration": "ie",
      "Answer": "house"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ヘヤ",
      "Narration": "heya",
      "Answer": "room"
    },
    {
      "Question": "マド",
      "Narration": "mado",
      "Answer": "window"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ツクエ",
      "Narration": "tsukue",
      "Answer": "desk"
    },
    {
      "Question": "イス",
      "Narration": "isu",
      "Answer": "chair"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ト",
      "Narration": "to",
      "Answer": "door"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ユウビンキョク",
      "Narration": "yuubinkyoku",
      "Answer": "post office"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ビョウイン",
      "Narration": "byouin",
      "Answer": "hospital"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ホンヤ",
      "Narration": "honya",
      "Answer": "bookstore"
    },
    {
      "Question": "エイガカン",
      "Narration": "eigakan",
      "Answer": "movie theater"
    },
    {
      "Question": "コウバン",
      "Narration": "kouban",
      "Answer": "police box"
    },
    {
      "Question": "キッサテン",
      "Narration": "kissaten",
      "Answer": "cafe"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ビジュツカン",
      "Narration": "bijutsukan",
      "Answer": "art museum"
    },
    {
      "Question": "タベモノ",
      "Narration": "tabemono",
      "Answer": "food"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ノミモノ",
      "Narration": "nomimono",
      "Answer": "drink"
    },
    {
      "Question": "サケ",
      "Narration": "sake",
      "Answer": "alcohol"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ニク",
      "Narration": "niku",
      "Answer": "meat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ヤサイ",
      "Narration": "yasai",
      "Answer": "vegetable"
    },
    {
      "Question": "クダモノ",
      "Narration": "kudamono",
      "Answer": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "Question": "リンゴ",
      "Narration": "ringo",
      "Answer": "apple"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ミカン",
      "Narration": "mikan",
      "Answer": "mandarin orange"
    },
    {
      "Question": "バナナ",
      "Narration": "banana",
      "Answer": "banana"
    },
    {
      "Question": "イチゴ",
      "Narration": "ichigo",
      "Answer": "strawberry"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ブドウ",
      "Narration": "budou",
      "Answer": "grape"
    },
    {
      "Question": "スイカ",
      "Narration": "suika",
      "Answer": "watermelon"
    },
    {
      "Question": "メロン",
      "Narration": "meron",
      "Answer": "melon"
    },
    {
      "Question": "モモ",
      "Narration": "momo",
      "Answer": "peach"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ミソ",
      "Narration": "miso",
      "Answer": "miso"
    },
    {
      "Question": "シオ",
      "Narration": "shio",
      "Answer": "salt"
    },
    {
      "Question": "サトウ",
      "Narration": "satou",
      "Answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ショウユ",
      "Narration": "shouyu",
      "Answer": "soy sauce"
    },
    {
      "Question": "コショウ",
      "Narration": "koshou",
      "Answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
      "Question": "サカナ",
      "Narration": "sakana",
      "Answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ニク",
      "Narration": "niku",
      "Answer": "meat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "タマゴ",
      "Narration": "tamago",
      "Answer": "egg"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ニンジン",
      "Narration": "ninjin",
      "Answer": "carrot"
    },
    {
      "Question": "タマネギ",
      "Narration": "tamanegi",
      "Answer": "onion"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ジャガイモ",
      "Narration": "jagaimo",
      "Answer": "potato"
    },
    {
      "Question": "サトウ",
      "Narration": "satou",
      "Answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
      "Question": "シオ",
      "Narration": "shio",
      "Answer": "salt"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ス",
      "Narration": "su",
      "Answer": "vinegar"
    },
    {
      "Question": "コメ",
      "Narration": "kome",
      "Answer": "rice"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ミソ",
      "Narration": "miso",
      "Answer": "miso"
    }
  ]
}